Guide to the Clarke Family Papers, 1904-1968 M0292
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photos (Box I)
  - 20) Photo - Chinese art (Chair), 2 copies
  - 21) 3 Photos - of Clarkes
  - 22) Photo - Chinese School
  - 23) Photo - China Medical Missionary association Conference, 1910